blahhotel.com 2015-10-03

# DomesticSale.com - Privacy Policy

## Privacy policy

DomesticSale has established its privacy policy to explain how your information within the purview of DomesticSale is protected, collected and used. This policy may be updated by DomesticSale. DomesticSale will post notices of its policy changes on the DomesticSale site at: <https://www.domesticsale.com/help-privacy.html>

**PRIVACY PROTECTION**

DomesticSale does not share your information with third parties for marketing purposes, or engage in cross-marketing or link-referral programs with other similar sites. DomesticSale recommends its customers to keep their password safe and do not remember it on public (shared) computers (Internet-cafe, college, library, family computer etc). DomesticSale does not knowingly collect any information from persons under the age of 13. If DomesticSale learns that a posting is by a person under the age of 13, DomesticSale will remove that posting. DomesticSale, or persons who post on DomesticSale, may provide links to third party websites, with different privacy policies. DomesticSale is not responsible for, nor have any control over, those third party websites. 

**INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE**

DomesticSale collect traditional contact information such as your name, mailing and/or billing address, phone number and email address for few purposes: to send selfpublishing and confirmation emails, to authenticate user accounts, to provide subscription email services, to register for forums, to process any credit card charges, etc.

DomesticSale does not store full credit card information but DomesticSale may store the information partially, such as only last 4 digits of your credit card number for transactions authenticating, monitoring and fraud prevention purpose. All credit card transactions initiated by DomesticSale are transmitted through a financial gateway using encrypted Secure Socket Layer (SSL 128 Bit) protocol.

Your personal information may be collected by DomesticSale if you provide it in the feedback or comments, post it on our classifieds, forums, guestbook or other publishing areas of the website.

Should you expect your personal information to be private please do not post any personal information on DomesticSale site. Standard web log entries for each page served, including visitor’s IP address, page URL, and timestamp are collected by DomesticSale web logs in order to help diagnose problem with DomesticSale servers, to administer DomesticSale site, and to otherwise enhance visitor’s use of DomesticSale sites and services. 

**DATA STORAGE**

DomesticSale stores in its database all user generated content (classified ads, forums, guestbook postings etc.) even after they are deleted, as well as can archive such data elsewhere. DomesticSale indefinitely stores web logs and other records. Registered members can access and update personal account information through the account homepage. 

**DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

DomesticSale may disclose information about its users if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process. DomesticSale may also disclose information about its users to law enforcement officers or others, in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to: enforce our Terms of Use; respond to claims that any posting or other content violates the rights of third-party; or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of DomesticSale, its users or the general public. DomesticSale complies with the provisions of C.R.S. § 6-1-716 pertinent to the breaches of security notifications effective September 1st, 2006. 

**GLOBAL USE**

By providing us with data and by visiting DomesticSale you acknowledge and agree that due to the global use of DomesticSale we may use the data collected in the course of your use of our site and/or services for the purposes identified in this policy or in our other communications to you, including the transmission of information outside your resident jurisdiction. Data provided to DomesticSale may be stored on servers throughout different jurisdictions. User agrees to consent to transfer of such data to different locations. 

**IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH DOMESTICSALE PRIVACY POLICY PLEASE LEAVE THIS WEBSITE**

Member area

Testimonials

I love this site too! The guy who set this up **really knows** what we shoe people need. Thanks!! :)  
ELENITA SCHNEIDER 

**Thank you** for helping me find a new home for my puppy! I placed the ad on the 13th and **got 180 responses in 2 days!** I was able to interview to find the PERFECT home on the 16th!  
Rebecca  
_Gainesville, Florida_

I was having a difficult time selling my pups...then I added them to Domesticsale.com. **Within 2 weeks they were sold**. I had over 300 hits! I'll come here first next time! Thanks so much!  
_Mineral Wells, WV_

This is a very nice site, I **sold my car** in few days!!!  
Thank You. Steve.
